<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Latest Music Scene</string>
    <string name="txtSundance2020Title">Sundance 2020: ‘The Go-Go’s’ Gives ’80s New Wave Band a Proper Music Doc (Finally)</string>
    <string name="txtSundance2020ImgDescription">A picture of The Go-Go\'s</string>
    <string name="txtButtons">View story</string>
    <string name="txtDiddyGrammysTitle">Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs: “Black Music Has Never Been Respected By The Grammys”</string>
    <string name="txtDiddyGrammysImgDescription">Diddy behind a microphone with his left hand up</string>
    <string name="txtSundanceArticleParagraph">Even if you’ve seen the footage before, in L.A. punk docs and VH-1 specials, it’s still thrilling to watch: Five women on stage, their outfits resembling a day-glo mix of thrift-store chic and a temper tantrum’s aftermath, two different kinds of eyeshadow and smeared streaks of rouge fighting for dominance, bashing out crude anthems at the Masque Club. “They played three songs, and two of them were the same song,” one witness remembers about that gig. They might be just another band who saw the Germs or the Weirdos or any of the first wave of those Decline of Western Civilization-era groups and decided they, too, could do it themselves. But that heavily mascaraed cherubic face shrieking into the microphone looks awfully familiar. So does the guitar player with the dark pixie cut. It’s Belinda Carlisle and Jane Wiedlin. This is the Go-Go’s 1.0.</string>
    <string name="txtDiddyGrammysArticleParagraph">Taking over the annual pre-Grammy party hosted by Clive Davis, Combs delivered a 50-minute speech that aired his grievances with the Recording Academy. His sentiments may be a prelude to other diatribes during tonight’s televised event, which are being held in the shadow of a legal battle with former CEO Deborah Dugan and the Recording Academy’s Board of Directors. Accusations of voting irregularities, sexism and cronyism have been floated in the dispute.</string>
</resources>
